ASIMUL HUDA

WordPress Developer

devasimulhuda@gmail.com
+8801327049921
🧕 3100 Sylhet, Bangladesh
in linkedin.com/in/asimulhuda/

OVERVIEW

A highly skilled and proficient WordPress developer with over 3 years of professional experience in all aspects of WordPress website creation, including design, plug-ins, and implementation. Results-driven individual contributor with a successful track record in exceeding expectations for web development initiatives. I am well organized and can deal with difficult situations while working under pressure to meet targets. Will show commitment to any employer for whom I work, possessing a positive attitude and ability to fit in quickly.

EDUCATION

High School (S.S.C)

Siraj Uddin Ahmed Academy 2015 - 2020

H.S.C Acconting

Israb Ali High School & College 2021 - on going

WordPress Development

Freelancerlab 2020 - 2020

KEYSKILLS

HTML

CSS

Bootstrap

WordPress Knowledge

WordPress Customization

WordPress Design

WordPress Proficiency

Woocommerce Proficiency

WordPress Plugin

Responsive Design

Front-End Development

Photoshop

Figma

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

WORDPRESS DEVELOPER (Freelance)

Freelancerlab | Sylhet, Bangladesh

June, 2020 - Dec, 2021

- Freelancerlab is a web design agency specializing in rapid development of WordPress websites for small companies.
- Developed several Websites with Bootstrap Framework and WordPress, HTML5, and
- Designed and developed more than 110 client websites with WordPress.

WORDPRESS DEVELOPER (Freelance)

Infinite Deal I Texas, USA

Jan, 2022 - April, 2023

- Infinite Deal is a global freelancing platform where businesses and independent professionals connect and collaborate remotely.
- Developed several Websites with Bootstrap Framework and WordPress, HTML5, and
- Designed and developed more than 90 client websites with WordPress.

WORDPRESS DEVELOPER (Freelance)

Vibe Branding | Brooklyn, USA

May, 2023 - current working (Part Time)

- Optimized website loading time performance by 2 times faster.
- Developed several Websites with Bootstrap Framework and WordPress, HTML5, and
- Designed and developed more than lots of client websites with WordPress.

LANGUAGES

EnglishBangla

Hindi

Urdu

REFERENCES

Available on request.